-
- "A
- "Ark
- "Ark 1
- "Ark 1"
- "Ark 1" is
- "Ark 1" is t
- "Ark 1" is the
- "Ark 1" is the f
- "Ark 1" is the fir
- "Ark 1" is the first
- "Ark 1" is the first o
- "Ark 1" is the first of
a
a lo
- "Ark 1" is the first of
a long
a long l
- "Ark 1" is the first of
a long lin
a long line
- "Ark 1" is the first of
a long line of
a long line of s
- "Ark 1" is the first of
a long line of spa
a long line of space
- "Ark 1" is the first of
a long line of spacecr
a long line of spacecraf
- "Ark 1" is the first of
a long line of spacecraft
fleeing a failing Earth
in search of a new planet
to call home.
The crew was tested
along the way.
- Lane!
- These implants,
they give her
some kind of
superhuman strength?
- I thought you were dead.
- What are you talking about?
- What, you really didn't
know you were a clone?
- We were able to make peace
with the rebel
Eastern Federation.
- This is Captain Zed Avega.
- Come with us.
- Together,
we made it to Trappist-1D.
- There's obviously water
and the atmosphere
is similar to Earth.
- But the team at Homebase
has begun to discover
that our new home
holds secrets of its own.
Other ships are still out
there looking for a home.
"Ark 1" won't stop
searching for them
until they bring them back
to Homebase.
- Do not come to Ross!
Turn around before
it's too late!
- So set a course for Ross?
- Their message sounded
like they're in trouble.
- Well, exactly. It said
do not come here, didn't it?
- Ian, our mission is
to find people who need help
and take them to Homebase 1.
- I say we go.
[suspenseful music]
- Alicia, are we close
enough yet to get more
information on the situation?
♪ ♪
- Still too far
for planetary readings,
but we've moved
into range to get
some readings on the Ross sun.
It's throwing off some
really severe solar storms.
- Meaning?
- "Ark 4" doesn't have the
long-range sensors we do.
It wouldn't have been able
to detect the solar storms
until it was too late.
- Too late for what?
- Solar storms at that level
would have knocked out
all life support
and electrical systems
on "Ark 4" before
it dropped out of FTL.
- So they're all dead?
- Not necessarily.
It's possible they
made it to the surface
before the storm started.
- But wouldn't the solar storm
still be bad
down on the planet?
- The atmosphere would protect
the crew from radiation.
- Then there might
be survivors.
- Wait. If we go,
won't our life support systems
just be fried like theirs was?
- Actually,
I've been working on a way
to rig the artificial
gravity generator
to project some
of its gravitons
onto the exterior of the ship.
- Which would do what?
- It would act as a shield
against the solar storms.
- There's a "but" coming.
I can always sense when
there's a "but" on the way out
of that little mouth of hers.
- No "but." It'll work.
- Great.
- For three hours.
- And there it is.
- That wasn't a "but."
- All right,
then we'll move fast
and use those three hours
to search for survivors.
How long until we're there?
- Two hours.
- Call me when we're close.
[peaceful music]
♪ ♪
- Mr. Trust!
You're not gonna believe
this slab we dug up!
Oh, man.
Angus to Mr. Trust.
Mr. Trust!
- The man never
answers his WD.
So annoying.
- All right.
Uh-- sorry, can you just--
- Yeah.
- Thank you so much.
[keypad beeping]
OK.
Thank you so much.
Oh, that's so cool.
[keypad beeping]
OK, let's just go find him.
- OK.
[tense music]
- All right.
- Hi, James.
You're right on time.
- Eva.
Wow, you uh-- [chuckles]
You look absolutely ravishing.
- Well, I wanted to look
my best for our celebration.
- Oh, yeah?
What we celebrating?
- Our one-year anniversary.
You kissed me for the first
time exactly a year ago.
- Huh.
Is that right?
Exactly?
- [chuckles]
OK, about a year ago.
Just go with it.
- All right,
all right, all right.
- So look what I found at
the Homebase exchange office.
A woman from "Ark 11"
was trading it.
- Oh!
Oh!
Wait, do-- do you know how
many light years away from me
you are right now?
That is just so cruel.
- Just pretend
I'm right there with you.
- Oh, baby, I want to.
I really, like, really do.
But, um--[clicks tongue]
Listen, could we maybe save
this for tomorrow's call?
- What?
- Because we're about
to land at Ross,
and I don't really
have any time.
I just wanted to see your face
before we go down
to the planet.
- You're going down there?
Is it safe?
- Is it safe?
Y-yes.
Yes, of course it's safe.
Listen, I'll tell you
all about it tomorrow, OK?
- All personnel, we arrive
at Ross in ten minutes.
- [sighs]
All right, I gotta go.
I love you.
- I love you, too.
- [chuckles]
- All these times
we've been in an FTL bubble,
I never realized
how beautiful it is.
- Yeah.
It is kind of stunning,
isn't it, Curly?
- Curly?
- Yeah, that was
my nickname for you
when we were in the coma dream
together.
You remember.
- No, I don't.
- Well, sure you do.
You loved it.
- I really doubt that.
- Yeah, I started
calling you Curly when
we were about 20 years in.
We were deep into
our romance by then.
- Hmm.
Did I call you something?
- Yeah.
Ian.
- [chuckles]
Oh.
Ian, we've been through this.
- [sighs]
You still hung up
on the whole
it was just a dream thing.
- It was just a dream.
- Maybe.
But a wonderful, beautiful,
romantic dream.
- [chuckles]
OK, yes, it was.
But, Ian, it wasn't real.
- Feelings I was left with
felt pretty real to me.
And I think they're
real for you, too.
You just won't admit it
for some reason.
- I'm sorry.
OK?
I'm dealing with a delicate
balance on this ship now,
commanding former GSA
and EF personnel
who just weeks ago
were enemies.
And somehow, God knows how,
I've managed
to gain their trust, and I--
I don't want to squander it.
- And being seen to be
in a romantic relationship
with a member of your crew
ain't very professional.
I get it.
♪ ♪
- We're at Ross.
Let's get to the bridge.
♪ ♪
Report.
- The solar shields
are working.
- Good job, Alicia.
- The scans are showing
no signs of life
on the parts of "Ark 4"
still in orbit.
It's not responding
to remote commands.
Electrics are fried.
- That includes life support,
I'm afraid.
- So everyone is dead?
- On the section
still in orbit, yes.
But they managed to get
two of their aft sections
and a center section
to the surface.
I'm guessing before
the solar storms hit.
- Any signs of life?
- Yes.
There are several life signs.
We may have gotten
here in time.
- All right.
Let's go find them.
Kimi, Brice, you're with me.
Dr. Morozov,
meet us in the shuttle dock
for a rescue mission.
Full EVA suits
and security batons.
- The shields will hold for
another 2 hours and 52 minutes,
so hurry.
- OK.
- I'm coming with you.
- No, you're not.
Alicia might need your
help with engineering.
- Sharon.
Be careful down there.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Looks kind of like Homebase.
- Earth-like planets were
the only ones selected
for colonies, Dr. Morozov.
- Oh, I'm technically
not a doctor.
More a field medic.
But people still call me Doc.
- Doc it is.
I'm sorry we didn't get
a chance to talk more
before being thrown into
the fire together.
Could that damage
be from the landing?
- Probably not.
The lower structures designed
for touchdown look intact.
- Does that mean
something caused
the damage after they landed?
- Could be.
Eyes open, folks.
Let's stay safe.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
- The air inside is safe.
We should take off the helmets
so we don't overheat.
- [sighs]
- How about we take off
the whole damn suit?
- Fine by me.
I should warn you I'm not
wearing anything underneath.
- You guys smell that?
- [sniffs]
- [coughs]
Oh, God.
- Oh, the stench.
♪ ♪
- These are some
really deep wounds.
- Like from the
building collapsing?
- More like someone
sliced and diced them.
- That can't be good.
- I wonder who they
armed themselves against.
- I don't know,
but let's do the same.
♪ ♪
- Doc, scan to see
if anyone is alive.
♪ ♪
[scanner beeping]
[scanner chimes]
♪ ♪
Anyone?
Let's keep moving.
[tense music]
[low chime]
- An X10-class flare.
- Well, what does that mean?
- Means the shields
took a big hit.
They won't last as long
as I thought.
We have to tell the surface
team they have less time.
- No, wait. I might have an
idea that could buy them more.
[laughs]
- You do?
- Yeah.
Don't sound too surprised.
I know a lot about
graviton generators.
- Oh, my God,
what are you doing?
- What?
- Those commands would have
turned off the
artificial gravity.
We'd all be floating
on the ceiling.
- Wait, really?
- Yes.
It wouldn't have
helped the shields at all.
- Uh, I mean, I guess I must
be off my game a bit.
I'm sorry.
- We'll have to think
of something else.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[scanner beeping]
- They're all dead.
Similar wounds.
- What the hell did this?
[distant thud]
- Hey, did you guys hear that?
- Defensive formation.
Kimi, take rear.
Doc, stay in the middle.
♪ ♪
[distant thud]
- I told you not to come.
-
- Wh
- Why
- Why di
- Why didn
- Why didn't
- Why didn't t
- Why didn't the
- Why didn't the c
- Why didn't the col
- Why didn't the colon
- Why didn't the colony
ch
chec
- Why didn't the colony
check
check th
- Why didn't the colony
check the
check the ai
- Why didn't the colony
check the air
check the air ea
- Why didn't the colony
check the air earl
check the air earlie
- Why didn't the colony
check the air earlier?
- They did, but I don't trust
any study done under Maddox,
so I'm double-checking it.
- Roger that.
5 kilometers out
from the sanitation zone.
- Nitrogen, 77%, oxygen 21.8,
carbon dioxide, 0.02,
and 4% water vapor.
The air could not
be more perfect.
- Almost like it was
made just for us.
- Let me know when we turn out.
[soft suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry about your brother.
I know he loved you very much.
He never stopped
searching for you.
- Thank you, sir.
- We're all civilians now.
I'm not your commanding officer
anymore.
My given name is Zed.
- OK.
- 10 kilometers.
[beeping]
Look, Eva--
may I call you Eva?
- Yes.
- Eva, I want you to know that
the EF and the GSA
don't exist anymore.
All that's behind us now.
- Yes, sir.
I mean Zed.
- Mm.
- Any luck finding
the other EF ship?
- "EF1"?
No.
We've been trying to raise
them, but no response.
- I had a lot of friends
on there.
- My son is on that ship.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- How far are we now?
- 14 kilometers from
the sanitation zone.
- The readings out here have
changed from Maddox's readings.
Air quality is decaying.
Oxygen is down to
almost half what it was.
Carbon dioxide
and nitrogen are up.
And the rest is just argon
and--and sulfuric acid.
- Why would that be?
- I don't know.
- 21k. Check it now.
- It's worse.
8% O2.
Sulfuric acid is rising.
- So what does this mean?
- It means we can only
expand the exploration zone
out to 15k.
Any more, and we won't
be able to breathe.
- We should check it
every day or so,
make sure the bad air
isn't expanding towards us.
- It better not be.
Or it could mean the end
of our peaceful little colony.
[laughter]
- No, seriously.
No.
I didn't make it up.
Honestly, I can't believe
you've never heard
the term afternoon delight.
- Mm, nope.
- Hmm.
- But it's very descriptive.
- Mm-hmm.
[chuckles]
- Matter of fact,
I'd like some more
of that delight.
- Now?
- Yeah.
- But again?
I don't want you
to burn out on me.
- Oh, never.
- [chuckles]
- I love you too much for that.
- You do?
- Yeah.
[soft dramatic music]
- Me too.
[chuckles]
- So we should only
widen the exploration zone
10 kilometers out,
but the air is safe out to 15k.
- Then we should start
exploring the exploration zone
out to that limit immediately.
- I don't agree.
It's not safe to go outside
our established zone.
- We're explorers.
We can't explore our new planet
without venturing
outside our comfort zone.
- And now that my ship's
population have offloaded,
there's far too many of us
crowded in a tight space.
And hopefully, "EF1" will
be arriving shortly.
We need to expand
our footprint.
- [whispering]
- Two men and a woman were
beaten today
walking down the street.
- Why?
- For the crime
of having been EF.
- I'm sorry, Mr. Avega.
Old animosities die hard.
- Well, it has to stop.
I don't have time
to keep breaking up fights.
I have too much on
my plate as it is.
- OK, then we'll find
someone else
to take charge
of law enforcement.
- Agreed.
Do you have someone in mind?
- I might.
- OK, I've cleaned the tablet
and ran a series of tests.
- And?
- Don't you get it, Mr. Trust?
I mean, the--
dude, I made the biggest
discovery in human history!
Oh, I can't wait
to tell everyone.
- All right.
Slow down, kid.
A lot of people won't be
as excited about this,
and some will find
it downright scary.
It'd be wise not to tell
anyone until we know more.
- OK.
Well, I ran the
text from the tablet
through every database we have
from both GSA and EF,
and I ran it through
an AI translator.
No luck deciphering it.
- And I'll be
testing the material.
- Whoa! Hey!
What are you doing?
- It's a machined alloy,
and it's stronger
than any material
I've ever heard of.
- Machined?
- Yep.
Which must mean that it was
made by an advanced society.
And the composite has an
element which I can't identify,
so it's probably
not from Earth.
- Duh.
Dude, it's got
alien writing on it.
- We don't know it's alien.
- What else could it be?
- Gentlemen,
meet Milan Petrovic.
Felix, he held
the same position you did,
but on my Ark.
- Civilian head of security?
- And I can vouch for the fact
that he was quite good at it.
- I see you were a police
officer on Earth for 12 years.
- Tough time to be a cop,
when things were falling apart.
- Yes, yes.
It was, um, rough times.
Everyone was panicking.
- I'd like to take a day to ask
around, do a little vetting.
- Wasn't he vetted by the GSA?
If I'm willing to accept that,
surely you would be.
- Are you?
- I'm willing to
accept him in the role.
As long as some of
his subordinates
are former EF security.
- That seems fair.
- Then, you have a new job,
Mr. Petrovic.
Head of Homebase One Security.
- It'll be my pleasure.
- As the colony is
a frontier town of sorts,
might I suggest his title
be Sheriff?
- [chuckles]
Sheriff Petrovic, you can start
by taking over responsibility
for the two people
we're holding in the jail.
- Consider it done,
Mr. Strickland.
[peaceful music]
♪ ♪
[birds singing]
[sighs] Hello, ladies.
I'm Sheriff Petrovic.
- Great.
Keeps getting better.
- Hi.
- I've been told I have
to check on you two.
Step back from the door.
- Like what you see?
- [scoffs]
I just wanted to make sure
you've been treated well.
- Oh, I'm treated
like royalty here.
Look around.
[dramatic music]
[scoffs]
You're not very good
at your new job, Sheriff.
- Sheriff, everything OK?
Sir?
[shouts]
♪ ♪
- Mm-mm.
- [groans]
♪ ♪
[metallic creaking]
[s
[sus
[suspe
[suspens
[suspensef
[suspenseful
[suspenseful m
[suspenseful mus
[suspenseful music
[suspenseful music]
- [groans]
- Come here, mate.
- I can walk.
- Your leg
doesn't look so good.
- I'll live.
- Sir, this is
Lieutenant Kimi Joma.
- Lieutenant James Brice.
- Medic Olga Morozov.
- And I'm Sharon Garnet,
captain of "Ark 1."
- Admiral Ben Hammond,
commanding officer
of "Ark 4."
- Admiral.
- Forgive me, sir.
I didn't realize your rank.
- What happened
to Captain Lester?
- Uh, she's dead.
- Well, Lester would have
listened to me and not come.
- Yeah, well,
aren't you glad we did?
Just a little bit?
- Are there any
other survivors?
- No.
We only made it down
with two aft sections
before the solar storms hit,
so there weren't many
of us to start with.
And I fought next to them
until every last one of them
was dead.
- Fought who, exactly?
[distant thud]
[distant growl]
- They've done so much damage
to the structural integrity
of this place, I'm surprised
it hasn't collapsed.
- Again, who is "they"?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- We have to hide.
They come out at night time.
- Who does?
[snarling]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Run!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
♪ ♪
Come on! Come on!
[tense music]
[growling]
♪ ♪
- What are those creatures?
- Indigenous animals
that we didn't know about
until after we got here
when they attacked.
The only reason why
we held on at all
was because my science officer
figured out
that they avoid sunlight
like fire.
- So why didn't you flee
during sunlight?
- The solar storms
trashed our shuttles.
Now those creatures are
trashing any shelter we have.
- Well, good news is
we have an intact shuttle.
- [sighs] I can't wait to tell
Eva about those things.
- Really?
Telling Eva is the first
thing on your mind right now?
Wow, man, you got it bad.
- What the hell
are you on about?
This is a huge deal.
We're the first human beings
to ever see alien life.
Except the "Ark 4" people.
Sorry.
- Well, you can tell Eva
on your next nookie call,
but first, we got to
get out of this alive.
- You know about the calls?
- I'm in the next cabin,
remember?
- The walls are pretty thin.
♪ ♪
[thud and rumbling]
- I doubt this building's going
to hold out until sunrise.
♪ ♪
- Garnet to Alicia and Ian.
- We're here, Captain.
- H-how's it going
down there, Sharon?
- Not so good.
We're pinned down
and won't be able to make it
to the shuttle until sunrise.
- Wait.
Pinned down by what?
- Alien bloody creatures, mate.
Can you believe it?
- Oh, really? Cool.
What do they look like?
- All we know is they have
an aversion to sunlight,
so we have to wait
until the sun comes out
to make a run for it.
[keyboard clicks]
- Captain Garnet,
the sun won't come up there
for another five hours.
The shields will hold
approximately one hour,
three minutes.
- Alicia, I'm going to need you
to figure out a way
to make them last longer.
- Yeah? Do you not think we've
already been trying to do that?
- We'll keep working on it.
- Keep me informed.
Garnet out.
- All right, come on.
Come on.
We've got this.
I've spent 50 years
studying solar storms.
I know everything about them.
All we have to do is change the
polarity on the Gravelaxacon,
and we can--
Wait. I'm listening to this
as I'm saying it.
It's all garbage, isn't it?
- It was a dream, Ian.
Anything you think
you taught yourself
was your brain making stuff up.
- Yeah, right.
It wasn't real.
None of it was.
- Ian, focus!
We need to figure this out.
Otherwise, we're going
to have to abandon them
to save the rest of the crew.
[thud and rumbling]
- Sharon, we're going to
have to make a run for it.
- Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
OK, Kimi and I will
lay down cover fire
to keep the creatures away
as you and the doc help
the admiral to the shuttle.
We can figure out--
- There's no way
to lay down cover fire.
Bullets don't hurt them.
- Then what do you suggest?
- Well, we can all leave this
room during the darkness,
and we'll get
shredded to death.
Or--
[groans]
We can stay in here.
And be crushed to death when
this building collapses on us.
Depends on how you want to die.
- Bet he's fun at parties.
[s
[sus
[suspe
[suspens
[suspensef
[suspenseful
[suspenseful m
[suspenseful mus
[suspenseful music
[suspenseful music]
- Hey.
Hey!
Somebody help me out of here!
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- Sorry. It took me
a minute to find her.
You OK, Sheriff?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
♪ ♪
- Don't worry.
I won't go anywhere.
- Why don't you
tell me your story?
- [chuckles]
Got a few days?
- I've done some bad things.
♪ ♪
- Me too.
[sighs]
But people change.
♪ ♪
I believe Kelly Fowler
should be freed.
- And why do you
suddenly feel this way?
- [sighs] As I said, she
captured a fugitive for me
without my even asking,
then returned to her own cell.
Seems pretty trustworthy.
- Are you aware
of how many people
Kelly Fowler has murdered?
- Under direct control
of her mother.
May I remind you, Ves,
you have one of those Maddox's
chips inside your head,
which made you do
all sorts of things too.
- Not murder.
- Didn't Miss Fowler help save
the colony from Maddox's chips?
- Yes.
- And she saved my daughter.
Kelly has changed.
- Our people's safety
is my top priority.
- Ves, I believe Miss Fowler
could be a big help
in assuring safety.
She could be my assistant.
- And you'll take
full responsibility of her?
- Yes, I will.
- I'll vouch for her as well.
[soft dramatic music]
- [scoffs]
Well, then.
I guess I'm outnumbered.
Free her.
♪ ♪
- Yeah.
Well, there it is.
Personally, I think
the food is much,
much better at The Landing Pad
than at the mess hall.
Is, uh, is something wrong?
- Pretty sure everyone
here hates me.
- Kelly!
- [chuckles]
- There's at least one person
who doesn't hate you.
- Hi, Katheryn.
- Come. Eat with us.
- Yeah. Go on. Go on.
I'll get us all some food.
Come on.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Why are you
outside of the brig?
- The council decided
to let me out.
- She saved my life.
- You might have saved her,
but you killed my brother,
Nathan Stark.
- I'm sorry for that, but I was
under the control of my mother.
♪ ♪
- You should be dead.
- It's OK.
It's OK.
Wait here.
Kelly?
[somber music]
Why didn't you fight back?
- Because I would
have killed them.
That would have just
made things worse.
Sorry you had to see that,
Katheryn.
♪ ♪
- Hey, do you think we
have enough of this fungus?
- Uh--[chuckles]
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, I just want to
grab some of the moss
off that tree over there.
[peaceful music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, gross.
- Wonder what killed it.
- You know, I did a stint
in ornithology before botany,
and this bird looks exactly
like a Eurasian blackbird.
What are the odds
of a bird evolving here
to look just like
a Eurasian blackbird?
- We should take it,
run its DNA.
Ugh.
♪ ♪
[leaves rustling]
- What was that?
- You heard it too?
- Yeah.
Maybe we should go back.
- I think we have enough
samples for one day.
Come on.
[tense music]
-
- An
- Any
- Any pr
- Any prog
- Any progre
- Any progress
- Any progress,
- Any progress, Al
- Any progress, Alic
- Any progress, Alicia
- Any progress, Alicia?
-
- So
- Any progress, Alicia?
- Sorr
- Sorry.
- Any progress, Alicia?
- Sorry. I
- Sorry. I'm
- Any progress, Alicia?
- Sorry. I'm a
- Sorry. I'm afr
- Any progress, Alicia?
- Sorry. I'm afrai
- Sorry. I'm afraid
- Any progress, Alicia?
- Sorry. I'm afraid no
- Sorry. I'm afraid not.
We only have about 45 minutes
before I have to move the Ark.
- Are we going to die here?
- Hey, hey. No.
Right?
There's always a way out.
♪ ♪
Look, why don't they go?
They-- they save the shields.
They come back to get us
when the sun's out.
[impacts and growling]
♪ ♪
- Doesn't look like
we'd make it that long.
- Do I have to pull rank here?
Let your Ark go.
One more solar max could
wipe out their life support.
We don't want
anyone else sacrificed
for your mistake
in coming here.
- Hang on just a sec.
- He's right.
Alicia, Ian,
you have to go now.
It's too risky for you to stay.
- No.
No way.
- Ian, listen to me.
It's OK.
We'll find a way to survive.
OK?
You can come back.
- Look, no, Sharon!
Just--
[sighs]
Alicia, come on.
Just do that genius thing
you do and fix this.
- I'm sorry,
but I'm all out of ideas.
[tense music]
- Come on, Ian.
Wait.
I have an idea.
- Did it come from your dream?
- Those things down there,
they avoid sunlight, right?
- Yeah.
- So all we have to do
is create more sunlight.
- How?
- This Ark is equipped
with solar sails, isn't it?
- Yes, and they're
highly reflective.
- Reflective.
- Ian, you're a genius!
- Come on.
- Captain Garnet, we might
be able to use the solar sails
to reflect sunlight to the
surface, make a path for you.
- [chuckles]
Alicia, you little beauty.
- Do it.
- Sasha, move us
into higher orbit.
- Sounds like you've got
some smart people, Captain.
- Grab a helmet.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[creatures hissing]
- OK. Go.
♪ ♪
[creatures chittering]
[creatures growling]
♪ ♪
- Run!
- [screaming]
- Doc!
- Shit!
- Sails are
starting to burn up.
Hurry.
- Kimi, keep going!
- OK.
Let's go.
♪ ♪
- Any ideas?
- We're going to have
to go through the darkness.
- Shoot our way out?
- He said bullets
don't stop them.
- Yeah. Unless you got anything
else, I think we have to try.
- OK. Back-to-back
defensive formation.
Come on. Get behind me.
♪ ♪
- Sharon.
It has truly been
an honor serving with you.
- Likewise, James.
But we're going to continue
serving together, OK?
What, it's like,
only 25 meters?
- Listen, if you
make it out of this--
- James.
- If you make it out of this
and I don't...
you tell Eva I love her, OK?
- We're both making it
out of here, OK?
You ready?
- Ready.
- On three.
One, two, three.
[both screaming]
Brice, come on.
We're close.
Come on, Brice!
- Come on.
Yes!
- Yes!
Come on, let's get
to the shuttle.
- Uh-huh.
♪ ♪
Shit.
- Keep going. Back-to-back.
Come on.
[soft suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[chittering and growling]
- [shouting]
- Can you get to the shuttle?
I'm going to pull
them off this way.
- No!
Stay together!
- [shouting]
Follow me, you ugly bastard!
♪ ♪
[groans]
- Brice!
- [groaning]
♪ ♪
[screaming]
- Go prep the shuttle.
[somber dramatic music]
- No, no.
♪ ♪
- Run!
[groans]
- Captain!
Run!
- [yelps]
♪ ♪
- Come on, Captain.
Captain,
we have to keep moving.
- Brice!
- Come one, Captain!
We have to go!
Come on, Captain!
Come on!
- No! No!
- Now!
♪ ♪
- [panting]
- Brace for launch.
[engines rumbling]
-
- [p
- [pan
- [panti
- [panting
- [panting]
[somber music]
- Are you injured?
- No.
♪ ♪
[crying]
- Hey.
I'm starving.
Uh, do you have any of
those, um, mushroom burgers?
- Yeah, sure.
- Oh, and a--
a vodka with soda.
Thanks.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Can I join you?
- You shouldn't feel obligated.
- What does that mean?
- I know how much you hate me.
- I don't hate you.
Don't get me wrong.
I did hate you, but a lot
has happened since then.
Uh, I have to go out
in the exploration zone
to finish collecting plant
samples in the underbrush.
[soft suspenseful music]
You want to come?
- I don't need your pity,
Angus.
I'm fine.
- Nothing to do with pity.
I swear.
Gabby's too afraid
to go out there,
but I'd feel safer
if you came instead.
You know,
with your implants and all.
♪ ♪
- Can I finish
my sandwich first?
♪ ♪
[computer chimes]
- James, you're late.
I almost changed back into--
oh.
Captain Garnet?
- Eva, um--
[soft somber music]
I really wanted to
do this in person,
but I know you guys
have your regular calls,
so I thought I shouldn't wait.
- Just tell me, please.
- OK.
When we were making a run to
the shuttle to escape Ross,
James was attacked by some
indigenous creatures,
really big ones.
And--[sobs]
I'm so sorry, Eva,
but he's dead.
- [crying]
Are you sure?
♪ ♪
- And I wish--
oh, I wish I wasn't.
But I saw him die myself.
I'm so sorry, Eva.
♪ ♪
Right before
we made a run for it,
Brice told me to tell you
he loves you so much.
You know he did.
- [sobs]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Please send me the WD logs
and the hull camera files
from the shuttle and the Ark.
- Eva, you don't
want to see it.
It's pretty bad.
- Seeing it myself is the only
way I'll be able to accept it.
♪ ♪
- So how do you
like being free?
- I didn't really mind
being locked up.
At least no one bothered me.
[rustling]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Where are you going?
Kelly, come back.
- Did you hear that over there?
- Yes, which is why we should
be going the other way.
- Don't you want
to know what it is?
- No!
Not particularly.
- Come on, Angus.
That's why you brought me.
- [groans]
[rumbling, whooshing]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪